onmobile.com 2016-12-14

# OnMobile | Privacy Policy

OnMobile Global Limited and its subsidiaries (hereinafter referred as ‘OnMobile’), are committed to respect your privacy and choices while using our website. The statement highlights our privacy practices regarding Personal Information that we hold about you.

##### I. Personal Information we may collect and process:

For the purposes of this privacy statement, ‘Personal Information’ is any data which relates to an individual who may be identified from that data, or from a combination of a set of data, and other information which is or may be in possession of OnMobile.

In general, you may browse our website without providing any Personal Information about yourself. However, certain information such as your IP address, your computers’ operating system, and browser type may be collected in order to provide better usability, troubleshooting, site maintenance and to understand which parts of the website are visited and how frequently.

We are legally bound to ensure that the provisions and regulation laid in relevant laws are respected and adhered to. In case of specific business requirements, OnMobile may collect information, which includes Personal information for purpose of conducting legitimate business activities like provision of various services as subscribed by consumers etc. OnMobile is committed to ensure that information, which is deemed necessary to conduct such activities alone, is collected from consumers.

##### II. Data recipients, transfer, and disclosure of Personal Information:

OnMobile does not share your Personal Information with third parties for marketing purposes without seeking your prior permission. OnMobile will seek your consent prior to using or sharing Personal Information for any purpose beyond the requirement for which it was originally collected.

We may share your Personal Information within OnMobile or with any of its subsidiaries, business partners, service vendors, authorized third-party agents, or contractors located in any part of the world for the purposes of data processing, storage, or to provide a requested service or transaction.

OnMobile doesn’t contact consumers for marketing purposes or launch/promotion of new services. Should there be any such business requirements, OnMobile is committed to ensure that the relevant regulations are complied with.

When required, OnMobile may disclose Personal Information to external law enforcement bodies or regulatory authorities, in order to comply with legal obligations.

##### III. Use of cookies:

Cookies are small text files that, like most other Web servers, we place in your device that you use to access our website. This is done to recognize your device during a session or in your future visits to our website, primarily in order to provide better user experience.

##### Types of cookies used:

**Session cookie:** Session cookies remain only as long as a browsing session is active, and are intended to avoid user inconvenience during browsing. These cookies allow websites to link the actions of a user during a browser session and expire at the end of the browsing session. Session cookies also assist the user in navigating the website, and allow the user to access secure parts of the webpage when logged in.

**Persistent cookie:** Persistent cookies are stored on a user’s device even after termination of a browsing session. It helps in recalling the preferences or actions of the user. Persistent cookies are used for a variety of purposes such as retaining the visitor’s language and regional preference(s) at the end of each browsing session. 

We do not collect any personal identifiable information like name, contact details, Email addresses etc. on our website.

We will use cookies to identify how you arrived at our website, to sample what pages you found more interesting or relevant, navigational experience and patterns around our website to make it more effective and to derive choices on how to make it relevant for users

Depending on the type and settings of your browser, cookies may be accepted by default. Most Browsers accept cookies by default. You may change the settings of your browser to delete existing cookies or prevent future cookies from being automatically accepted. If you disable cookies, certain parts and functions of our website may not be available.

##### IV. Data Protection and Security

To prevent unauthorized and unlawful usage of your personal identifiable information, OnMobile has put in place reasonable and appropriate physical, organizational and technical solutions, practices and measures in place. OnMobile is committed to implement such further controls and technical measures in place from time to time as may be mandated by any regulatory authority or as may be required by the internal policies, practices and business requirements.

##### V. Data Retention & Disposal

OnMobile may retain your Personal Information as long as there is a business requirement, or if otherwise required under applicable laws. The information shall be disposed once the need is fulfilled or as per statement applicable under law.

##### VI. Linked websites

OnMobile may provide links to third-party websites and services. However, OnMobile is not responsible for the privacy statements, practices, or the contents of such third-party websites.

##### VII. Updates to this privacy statement

OnMobile may change the data privacy practices and update this privacy statement as and when the need arises and the same will be made available on the website. But our commitment to protect the privacy of website users will continue to remain.

Click here for more information about the Data Privacy Framework

In case of any queries or concerns regarding the privacy policy, you may please send an email to [privacy@onmobile.com](mailto:privacy@onmobile.com)
